

SCAN QR CODE TO VIEW PORTFOLIO

PERSONAL

NAME D.O.B RELATIONSHIP LANGUAGE NATIONALITY JOSHUA JONA NOV / 03 / 1989 SINGLE ENGLISH / SWAHILI KENYAN

CONTACTS

CELL E-MAIL +254706518030 emjaymuga@gmail.com

PRO. SKILLS

Graphic Design
Project Management
Social Media Marketing
Team work
Illustration
Brand Identity
IT Windows and Mac OS.

INTERESTS



Movies



Workout



Soccer



Music



JOSHUA JONA

ABOUT ME

I am inspired by all facets of design. I come up with visual creations that are compelling, communicate and professionally drawn.

Highly creative and multitalented Graphic Designer with broad experience in multimedia, marketing and print design. I have exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; dynamic team player with well developed written and verbal communication skills.

Accustomed to performing in deadline-driven environments with an emphasis on working within budgeted requirements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2011 - 2013, ADEO (AFRICAN DEVELEOPMENT EMERGENCY ORGANISATION) NAIROBI - IT/ Graphic Designer Responsibilities:

Creating visual content for outreach in communities. Database management and creation Print graphic design

2014 - 2017, POTENCY BRANDS - NAIROBI - Graphic Designer Responsibilities:

Graphic Design Logistics and Coordination Print and merchandize production quality control Bookkeeping and simple accounting

2018 - PRESENT, SILVEROAK STUDIOS - Creative Director Responsibilities:

Organizing creative processes and direction.
Marketing and Advertising.
Corporate design and branding.
Large format printing.
Publication design

EDUCATION

1995 - 2003, Toi Primary School, Nairobi. Sat for my Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

2003 - 2007, Secondary Education - Masii High School Sat for my Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

2008 - 2010, College Education - Nairobi Technical College Diploma in Graphic Communication & Advertising with IT

SKILL CHART

